Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Daily Records
1905 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Daily
UA176
13.65 Linear Feet 26 boxes
751 Digital Object(s) Of the 751 digital objects, 689 have extent information and comprise 15,137 files.
51.71 Gigabytes Of the 726 digital objects, 664 have extent information and comprise 51.71 GB.
This collection contains the records of the Tufts Daily.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Photographs; Negatives; Slides; 2018 accessions; Production files; and Podcasts and scripts.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Daily, founded in 1980, is the daily undergraduate student newspaper for Tufts University. Its mission is to provide a source of news for the Tufts community, a forum for the exchange of ideas, and a means for students to gain experience in journalism. It covers university news, sports, and events as well as some national and international news. It also includes editorials, a calendar of events, and syndicated comics. Published and distributed free of charge on class days during the academic year, the Tufts Daily is student-run and receives no financial support from Tufts University.
Particularly valuable are the Tufts Daily photographs documenting campus life - the people, places, events, and activities of Tufts University.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes photographic prints, negatives, slides, CD-Rs, and photograph and production files extracted from CD-R disks once used in the production of the Tufts Daily newspaper. It also contains documents, such as information sheets for the negatives, contact sheets, and office documentation, podcasts, and scripts. The predominant file formats in this collection include the following, in order of prevalence: Exif, TIFF, JPEG, Microsoft Word documents, plain text files, PDF, and QuarkXPress documents.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Tufts Daily, 2005 -- 2021.
Related Materials
UP029: Tufts Daily, 1980 -- 2020. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Student Activities -- Student Publishing; Student life; Student activism; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student Activities -- Athletics
- Photographs, 1980 -- 2009; UA176.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 556 Digital Object(s) Of 556 digital objects, 495 have extent information comprising 11,866 files.; 47.35 Gigabytes Of 555 digital objects, 495 have extent information comprising 47.35 GB.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  Arrangement
  This series is in the original order kept by the Daily staff. One portion is arranged alphabetically by person, organization, or place, and one portion is arranged alphabetically into categories by subject/sport. Digital material extracted from CD-Rs and processed in 2020 -- 2021 is arranged in chronological order. Original order has been maintained for all files.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains photographs taken by photographers for the Tufts Daily between 1980 and 2009. The predominant file formats in this series include the following, in order of prevalence: Exif, TIFF, and JPEG.
  - Photographs, A, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, B, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, C, 1999 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Professor Cantor, 2000; UA176.001.001.00003.00001; Vyavaharkar, Suni (Box 1)
      This date is approximate.
      Faculty; Cantor, Jay; Dept. of English
    - New Convenience Store, 1902 -- 1999; UA176.001.001.00003.00002; Wang-Iverson, Jeremy (Box 1)
      Buildings; Stores; Campus Convenience
  - Photographs, D, 2000 -- 2004; UA176.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Dowling Hall with covering newly removed, 2000 -- 2004; UA176.001.001.00004.00001; Silberberg, Jacob (Box 1)
      Parking lots; Construction
    - Dowling Hall construction site, 2000 -- 2002; UA176.001.001.00004.00002; Silberberg, Jacob (Box 1)
      Construction; People
    - Bridge to Dowling Hall (2 days old), 2000 -- 2001; UA176.001.001.00004.00003; Golub, Justin S. (Box 1)
      Construction; Bridges
  - Photographs, E, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, F, 1996 -- 2003; UA176.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - 'Faculty waits on you', 2003; UA176.001.001.00006.00001; Stitchbury, Brad (Box 1)
      People identified left to right. Frank Nocito (Res. Life) and Winnie Murray ('03). This date is approximate.
      Events; Faculty; Dinners and Dining; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Fire at 87 Electric Ave, 1910 -- 1996; UA176.001.001.00006.00002; Netto, Mike (Box 1)
      Fire; Buildings
  - Photographs, G, 2000 -- 2003; UA176.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Sol Gittleman, 2000; UA176.001.001.00007.00001; Unknown (Box 1)
      Professors; College administrators; Faculty; Gittleman, Sol, 1934-; Dept. of German, Russian, and Asian Languages and Literature
    - Tufts demonstrations at Gore rally, fans, 2000 -- 2003; UA176.001.001.00007.00002; Silberberg, Jacob (Box 1)
      Demonstrations; Political campaigns; Students; Gore, Albert
  - Photographs, H, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, I, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, J, 2000; UA176.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Jumbo the mascot, 2000; UA176.001.001.00010.00001 (Box 1)
      Mascots; Athletics
  - Photographs, K, 2000 -- 2004; UA176.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Kids Day 2000, 2000 -- 2004; UA176.001.001.00011.00001; Unknown (Box 1)
      Katie Cohen identified on back.
      Events; Children; Leonard Carmichael Society
  - Photographs, L, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, M, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, N, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, O, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, P, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, Q, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, R, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, S, 1989 -- 1999; UA176.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Bryan Shelly, 1997; UA176.001.001.00019.00001; Shram, Rony (Box 1)
      Image not for digital library.
      Students
    - Rabbi Summitt displays new Torah, 1910 -- 1989; UA176.001.001.00019.00002; Schatz, K (Box 1)
      Professors; Faculty; Summitt, Jeffrey; Dept. of German, Russian, and Asian Languages and Literature; Department of Music; Hillel Foundation
    - Rabbi Summit, 1995; UA176.001.001.00019.00003 (Box 1)
      Professors; Faculty; Summitt, Jeffrey; Dept. of German, Russian, and Asian Lang; Department of Music; Hillel Foundation
    - South Hall with crane, 1902 -- 1997; UA176.001.001.00019.00004; Netto, Mike (Box 1)
      Dormitories; Construction
    - Sweet Hall destruction, 1999; UA176.001.001.00019.00005; Anderson, Eric (Box 1)
      This data is approximate.
      Offices; Demolition sites
  - Photographs, T, 1989 -- 2003; UA176.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    - Sherman Teichman on the phone, 1902 -- 1989; UA176.001.001.00020.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
      Professors; Faculty; Teichman, Sherman
    - Sherman Teichman dancing, 1990; UA176.001.001.00020.00003; Unknown (Box 1)
      Professors; Faculty; Dances and Dancing; Teichman, Sherman
    - Sherman Teichman at a desk, 1990; UA176.001.001.00020.00004; Unknown (Box 1)
    - Students console each other at rally, 1903 -- 1999; UA176.001.001.00020.00005; Rogelberg, Steven (Box 1)
      Demonstrations; Student activities
    - Tuftonia's Day, 1904 -- 1990; UA176.001.001.00020.00006; Snyder, Brian (Box 1)
      Holidays; Alumni and alumnae
    - Drag show (TTLGBC), 2000 -- 2003; UA176.001.001.00020.00007; Golub, Justin S. (Box 1)
      Events; Drag shows; Students; TTLGBC
  - Photographs, U, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, V, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, W, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, Y, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, Z, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Baseball, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Basketball, men's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Basketball, women's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Celebrities, 1988 -- 2004; UA176.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Arthur Schlesinger, 2000; UA176.001.002.00004.00001; Kernohen, Tara (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Historians; Authors; Schlesinger, Arthur M. (Arthur Meier), 1888-1965
    - Arthur Sulzberger Jr. being awarded the Light on the Hill award, 1904 -- 1996; UA176.001.002.00004.00002; Tilston, Shane (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Alumni and alumnae; Sulzberger Jr., Arthur
    - Austin Pendleton (Actor), 2000; UA176.001.002.00004.00003; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Actors; Pendleton, Austin
    - Bobby Orr, 2000; UA176.001.002.00004.00004; Wolf, Oliver (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Hockey; Athletics; Orr, Bobby
    - Margaret Thatcher delivering a speech for the annual Issam Fares Lecture Series, 1998; UA176.001.002.00004.00005; Shram, Rony (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Politician; Thatcher, Margaret
    - Sam Donaldson, 1910 -- 1988; UA176.001.002.00004.00006; Drower, Denise (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Politics; Donaldson, Sam
    - Spike Lee at the the programming boards lecture series, 2004; UA176.001.002.00004.00007; Unknown (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Motion picture producers and directors; Lee, Spike; Tufts Literary Magazine
  - Club sports, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Coming-Out Day, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Crew, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Cross Country, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Daily office, staff, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - President DiBiaggio, 1998; UA176.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - President DiBiaggio, 1998; UA176.001.002.00010.00001; Shram, Rony (Box 2)
      College presidents; DiBiaggio, John A.
  - Faculty meetings, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Fall/Winter photos, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Football, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Fraternities and sororities, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Golf, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Graduation, 1996, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Lacrosse, men's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Lacrosse, women's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Library, 1995; UA176.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    - Construction site for Wessell Library, 1995; UA176.001.002.00021.00001; Tilston, Shane (Box 2)
      Construction; Libraries
    - Exterior view of construction for Wessell Library, 1995; UA176.001.002.00021.00002; Tilston, Shane (Box 2)
  - Music groups, 1995 -- 1998; UA176.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    - LL Cool J at Spring Fling, 1998; UA176.001.002.00022.00001; Lake, Lisa (Box 2)
      Performance artists; Music; LL Cool J
    - B.B. King at Spring Fling, 1995; UA176.001.002.00022.00002 (Box 2)
      Performance artists; Music; King, B. B.
  - Politicians, 1998 -- 2004; UA176.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    - Bill Bradley campaigns at the Fletcher School for Law and Diplomacy, 1999; UA176.001.002.00023.00001; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Politics; Basketball; Political campaigns; Bradley, Bill; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Bill Richardson, 1904 -- 1999; UA176.001.002.00023.00002; Unknown (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Politician; Alumni and alumnae; Richardson, Bill
    - Rob Kenney, John Kerry supporter, 2004; UA176.001.002.00023.00003 (Box 2)
      Political campaigns; Kenney, Rob
    - Rob Kenney and students, 2004; UA176.001.002.00023.00004; Unknown (Box 2)
      Political campaigns; Student activities; Kenney, Rob
    - Mike Capuano campaigns for Congress, 1910 -- 1998; UA176.001.002.00023.00005; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 2)
      Speeches; Political conventions; Political campaigns; Capuano, Mike
    - Senator John Kerry speaking for Earth month, 2000 -- 2004; UA176.001.002.00023.00006 (Box 2)
      Lecturers; Politician; Kerry, John
    - Senator John Kerry, 1902 -- 1998; UA176.001.002.00023.00007 (Box 2)
  - Professional sports, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Protests, rallies, and events, 1999 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
    - Cornel West, 1903 -- 1999; UA176.001.002.00025.00001; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 2)
      Professors; Lecturers; West, Cornel
    - Protest at Jiong speech, 2000; UA176.001.002.00025.00002 (Box 2)
      Demonstrations
  - Sailing, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Senate, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Soccer, men's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Soccer, women's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Softball, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Spring photos, 1999; UA176.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    - Snowman in spring, 1999; UA176.001.002.00031.00001 (Box 2)
      Snow; Student activities
  - Students, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Swimming, men's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Swimming, women's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Tennis, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Track, men's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Track, women's, 1980 -- 2000; UA176.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Twelfth Night, 2003; UA176.001.002.00039.000002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Volleyball, women's, 1996; UA176.001.002.00039.000001 (Box 2)
    - Jessica Stewart and Megan Pitcavage in volleyball game against MIT, 1996-10-28; UA176.001.002.00038.00001; Unknown (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "#5 Jessica Stewart; #14 Megan Pitcavage; 10/28 vs MIT; Kate Cohen
      Volleyball; photographic print; Stewart, Jessica; Pitcavage, Megan
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00002; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Mike Weissman"
      Volleyball; photographic print
    - Women playing volleyball against EAC, 1996-10-16; UA176.001.002.00038.00003; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "10/16 vs EAC; by Mike Weissman; pg 7; 58%; Bottom left"
    - Lis Drake playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00004; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "volleyball; Lis Drake; 83% 5A; By Eric Anderson"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996-10; UA176.001.002.00038.00005; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Volleyball 10/96; by Mike Weissman; IVA 43% and IE 20%"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00006; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Mike Weissman; 7B 60%"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00007; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Photo by Mike Weissman; 7A 68.5%"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00008; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Mike Weissman; 7A 83%"
    - Women's volleyball team huddle, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00009; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "W. volleyball; #2 Dana Cohen; #5 Jessica Stewart; 88% 7a; by Eric Anderson"
    - Melanie Winograd playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00010; Unknown (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Soph Melanie Winograd"
      Volleyball; photographic print; Winograd, Melanie
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00011; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Mike Weissman; 30% iva"
    - Woman hitting volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00012; Weissman, Mike (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Mike Weissman; 7B 39%"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00013; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "Volleyball; 105 % VIII 9; By Eric Anderson"
    - Women's volleyball game against MIT, 1996-10-28; UA176.001.002.00038.00014; Unknown (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: " #5 Jessica Stewart?; 10/28 vs MIT; Kate Cohen"
      Volleyball; photographic print; Stewart, Jessica
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00015; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "W Volleyball; 7A; By Eric Anderson"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00016; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "W Volleyball; 83% 7; 83% 5B; By Eric Anderson"
    - Megan Pitcavage and Dana Cohen playing volleyball against MIT, 1996-10-28; UA176.001.002.00038.00017; Unknown (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "#14 Megan Pitcavage; #2 Dana Cohen; 10/28 vs MIT - Kate Cohen"
      Volleyball; photographic print; Pitcavage, Megan; Cohen, Dana
    - Jessica Stewart playing volleyball, 1996; UA176.001.002.00038.00018; Anderson, Eric (Box 2)
      Back of print reads: "W. Volleyball; #5 Jessica Stewart; 115x166 50% 57.5x83; Photo by Eric Anderson"
  - Bacow Matriculation Address, 2001 August 29; UA176.001.002.00040; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.; 40.5 Kilobytes
  - OEO Fair CD, circa 2000; UA176.001.002.00041 (Box 122, 3, 7, 36)
    This item may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  - Aaron Gest RA Feature CD, 2003-10-02; UA176.001.002.00042 (Box 122, 3, 7, 36)
  - Photo archive, 2000 April 01 -- 2000 April 20; UA176.004555; 587.88 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 69 files.
    - Arts, 2000 April 01 -- 2000 April 20; UA176.004556; 63.53 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Features, 2000 April 01 -- 2000 April 20; UA176.004557; 40.55 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - News, 2000 April 01 -- 2000 April 20; UA176.004558; 355.68 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 32 files.
    - Sports, 2000 April 01 -- 2000 April 20; UA176.004559; 128.11 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 25 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 April 21 -- 2000 September 03; UA176.004560; 631.18 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 91 files.
    - Arts, 2000 April 21 -- 2000 September 03; UA176.004561; 37.23 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Features, 2000 April 21 -- 2000 September 03; UA176.004562; 26.59 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - News, 2000 April 21 -- 2000 September 03; UA176.004563; 406.55 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 44 files.
    - Sports, 2000 April 21 -- 2000 September 03; UA176.004564; 160.81 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 38 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 September 04 -- 2000 September 20; UA176.004565; 600.5 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 75 files.
    - Arts, 2000 September 04 -- 2000 September 20; UA176.004566; 75.63 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
    - Features, 2000 September 04 -- 2000 September 20; UA176.004567; 257.4 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 27 files.
    - News, 2000 September 04 -- 2000 September 20; UA176.004568; 216.85 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 29 files.
    - Sports, 2000 September 04 -- 2000 September 20; UA176.004569; 50.62 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 September 21 -- 2000 October 04; UA176.004570; 589.65 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 106 files.
    - Arts, 2000 September 21 -- 2000 October 04; UA176.004571; 21.39 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Features, 2000 September 21 -- 2000 October 04; UA176.004572; 164.1 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 23 files.
    - News, 2000 September 21 -- 2000 October 04; UA176.004573; 166.26 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 33 files.
    - Sports, 2000 September 21 -- 2000 October 04; UA176.004574; 237.9 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 47 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 October 04 -- 2000 October 13; UA176.004575; 452.37 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 56 files.
    - Arts, 2000 October 04 -- 2000 October 13; UA176.004576; 12.68 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Features, 2000 October 04 -- 2000 October 13; UA176.004577; 227.28 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 21 files.
    - News, 2000 October 04 -- 2000 October 13; UA176.004578; 112.15 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 19 files.
    - Sports, 2000 October 04 -- 2000 October 13; UA176.004579; 100.26 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 October 14; UA176.004580; 642.93 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 33 files.
    - News, 2000 October 14; UA176.004581; 11.85 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Sports, 2000 October 14; UA176.004582; 631.07 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 31 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 October 15 -- 2000 October 23; UA176.004583; 554.55 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 82 files.
    - Arts, 2000 October 15 -- 2000 October 23; UA176.004584; 44.15 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Features, 2000 October 15 -- 2000 October 23; UA176.004585; 99.57 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 16 files.
    - News, 2000 October 15 -- 2000 October 23; UA176.004586; 293.87 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 32 files.
    - Sports, 2000 October 15 -- 2000 October 23; UA176.004587; 116.96 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 30 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 October 24 -- 2000 October 30; UA176.004588; 568.42 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital object comprising 50 files.
    - Arts, 2000 October 24 -- 2000 October 30; UA176.004589; 2.54 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Features, 2000 October 24 -- 2000 October 30; UA176.004590; 381.01 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 31 files.
    - News, 2000 October 24 -- 2000 October 30; UA176.004591; 163.1 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 15 files.
    - Sports, 2000 October 24 -- 2000 October 30; UA176.004592; 21.76 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 October 31 -- 2000 November 08; UA176.004593; 635.37 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 81 files.
    - Arts, 2000 October 31 -- 2000 November 08; UA176.004594; 49.13 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Features, 2000 October 31 -- 2000 November 08; UA176.004595; 51.76 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - News, 2000 October 31 -- 2000 November 08; UA176.004596; 366.8 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 44 files.
    - Sports, 2000 October 31 -- 2000 November 08; UA176.004597; 167.68 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 24 files.
  - Photo archive, 2000 November 09 -- 2000 November 21; UA176.004598; 623.49 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects comprising 102 files.
    - Arts, 2000 November 09 -- 2000 November 21; UA176.004599; 45.52 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
    - Features, 2000 November 09 -- 2000 November 21; UA176.004600; 113.42 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 17 files.
    - News, 2000 November 09 -- 2000 November 21; UA176.004601; 164.44 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 24 files.